Gordon, Matthew Collection of Canadian Auto Workers Union Materials 6381
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Matthew Gordon Collection of Canadian Auto Workers Union Materials
1996- 2011
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Gordon, Matthew
Canadian Auto Workers Union (CAW)
6381
0.72 cubic feet
0.7 linear ft.
Records.
8468173
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, May 14, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 07, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
8468173
- Constitution, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Agreements: Local 99, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Agreements: Local 350, 2003-2006 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Agreements: Local 534, 1994-1997 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Agreements: Local 551, 1997-2009 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Agreements: Local 1112, 2001-2004 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Agreements: Local 4050, 1997-2011 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Agreements: Local 4325, 2005-2011 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- CAW Education Programs Booklet (Box 1, Folder 9)
- CAW Health and Safety, 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- CAW Sisterhood Pamphlets, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- PEL The Union Experience (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Searching for the Switch to Locking Out (Box 2, Folder 1)